https://www.pearsonsflorist.com.au/privacy-policy

By Type
Luxe Range Florist Choice Bouquets Flower Bottles Event & Party Flowers Corporate Hampers
Peonies Plants Plant Packs Native & Wild Flowers Dried & Preserved Flowers
YOUR PRIVACY
At pearsonsflorist.com.au, we are committed to protecting your privacy as an online visitor to our website. We use the information we collect about you to maximise the services that we provide to you. pearsonsflorist.com.au respects the privacy and confidentiality
of the information provided by you and adheres to the Australian Privacy Principles. Please read our separate Privacy Policy below carefully.
You may change your details at any time by advising us in writing via email. All information pearsonsflorist.com.au receives from its customers is protected by our secure server. pearsonsflorist.com.au’s secure server software encrypts all customer information
before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all customer data collected is secured against unauthorised use or access. Credit card information is not stored on our servers.
Personal Information refers to any information which may identify an individual personally, such as first and last name, home address, billing address, or other physical address, email address, telephone number, etc.
“User” refers to a visitor to Pearsons Florist websites. A User includes existing customers, new customers, and potential customers.
STORAGE AND SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION
We collect personal information that is reasonable or necessary to accomplish the purpose of your interaction with Pearsons Florist as a User, with the intention of improving the user experience and for providing you our Services.
As a User of Pearsons Florist Site, when you interact on Pearsons Florist Site, you entered into an agreement with Pearsons Florist to accept Pearsons Florist terms of use of the Services on our site. When you use Pearsons Florist Services, we may collect personally identifiable information as that of a User; information such as Name, Address, Mobile, non-transaction payment type information, and usage data in relation to the Services and other information we deem relevant for the purpose of providing the Services.
We receive and store information you enter on our website or give us in any other way from time to time. You may provide basic contact information such as your name, phone number, address, and email address to enable us to send information or process
your product order and we may also collect additional information at other times, including but not limited to, when you provide feedback, change your content or email preferences, respond to a survey, or communicate with pearsonsflorist.com.au
customer support or queries.
We may use personal information and data collected from you for the purpose of:
Send you communications about our Site or respond to inquiries.
Initiate communications to elicit your response regarding assistance from us on your user experience on our Site
Send you communications and updates about the Pearsons Florist Services, including newsletters.
Provide support for the Pearsons Florist Services
Enhance or improve user experience, our Site, or Pearsons Florist Services.
Perform any other function that we believe in good faith is necessary to protect the security or proper functioning of our Site or the Pearsons Florist Services.
such publications by your registering your details with us. However if you wish to cease receiving any such information you may let us know either by email or unsubscribing at any time and your request will be actioned as soon as possible.
Individual profile and company details are not used for any other purpose. Details are only supplied to a third party supplier when it is required by law, for goods or services which you have purchased or to protect pearsonsflorist.com.au copyright, trademarks
and other legal rights.
We respect the privacy of our online visitors. We may collect information on or through this website that can personally identify you. For example, we collect personally identifiable information which you volunteer to us to respond to visitor questions
and comments about us and our products and services, and to mail e-newsletters (“Personal Data”).
We may use your non-personal identifiable testimonials along with those of other satisfied customers on our Site in addition to other endorsements.
We will use all reasonable means to protect the confidentiality of your Personal Data while in our possession or control. We will not knowingly share any of your Personal Data with any third party other than our service providers who assist us in providing
the information and/or services we are providing to you. To the extent that we do share your personal information with a service provider, we would only do so if that party has agreed to comply with our privacy standards as described in this
privacy policy. Some of our service providers may be overseas and may not be subject to Australian Privacy Laws. Please contact us if you require specific details.
Any non-personal information, communications and material you send to this website or to us by email, or which we obtain from third parties without promises of confidentiality, may be kept, used and disclosed by us on a non-confidential basis. We are
free to use and reproduce any such information freely, and for any purpose whatsoever. Specifically, we will be free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques contained in such information for any purpose, including developing, manufacturing
or marketing products.
COOKIES
A cookie is a small file placed in your web browser that collects information about your web browsing behaviour. Use of cookies allows a website to tailor its configuration to your needs and preferences. Cookies do not access information stored on your
computer or any personal information (e.g. name, address, email address or telephone number). Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but you can choose to reject cookies by changing your browser settings. However, this may prevent
you from taking full advantage of a website.
Our website uses cookies to analyse website traffic and help us provide a better website visitor experience. In addition, cookies may be used to serve relevant ads to website visitors through third party services such as Google Adwords. These ads may
appear on this website or other websites you visit.
DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION
We may from time to time need to disclose certain information, which may include your Personal Data, to comply with a legal requirement, such as a law, regulation, court order, subpoena, warrant, in the course of a legal proceeding or in response to a
law enforcement agency request. Also, pearsonsflorist.com.au may use your Personal Data to protect the rights, property or safety of pearsonsflorist.com.au, its customers or third parties.
Finally, if there is a change of control in one of our businesses (whether by merger, sale, or otherwise), or a sale or transfer of its assets, customer information, which may include your Personal Data, could be disclosed to a potential purchaser under
an agreement to maintain confidentiality, or could be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. And finally we would only disclose your information in good faith and where required by any of the above circumstances.
THIRD PARTIES
pearsonsflorist.com.au does not and will not sell or deal in personal or customer information. We will never disclose your personal details to a third party except the necessary information required by providers of products or services you have purchased
or to protect the rights, property or safety of pearsonsflorist.com.au, its customers or third parties or if required by law.
We may however use in a general sense without any reference to your name, your information to create marketing statistics, identify user demands and to assist it in meeting customer needs generally. In addition, we may use the information that you provide
to improve our website and services but not for any other use.
SECURITY
pearsonsflorist.com.au strives to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of personal information submitted to our website, and periodically updates its security measures in light of current technologies. These measures include using SSL Certificates.
ANONYMITY
pearsonsflorist.com.au customers have the right to remain anonymous except in those transactions (such as Credit Card or Account sales) where personal information is required to complete such transactions. In the case of floral or gift deliveries pearsonsflorist.com.au
will not disclose the sender information to the recipient unless specifically requested to do so by the customer.
We treat the data of everyone who comes to our site in accordance with this Privacy Policy, regardless of their Do Not Track setting.
LINKS
This website may contain links to other websites. These links are meant for your convenience only. Links to third party websites do not constitute sponsorship or endorsement or approval of these websites. Please be aware that pearsonsflorist.com.au is
not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage our users to be aware, when they leave our website, to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.
This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.
REGISTERED CUSTOMER ACCOUNTS
You may register as pearsonsflorist.com.au customer when placing an order online. As a registered pearsonsflorist.com.au customer you may update, edit or terminate your customer account at any time. You agree to maintain and update the information as
supplied by yourself to ensure accuracy at all times. As a registered pearsonsflorist.com.au customer, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your own membership account and password. You agree to take responsibility for
all activities that occur under your membership account and password.
CHANGE IN PRIVACY POLICY
As we plan to ensure our privacy policy remains current, this policy is subject to change. We may modify this policy at any time, in our sole discretion and all modifications will be effective immediately upon our posting of the modifications on this
website. Please return periodically to review our privacy policy.
If you are a visitor to this Site and disagree with the Privacy Policy, you should leave the Site.
If you have any questions or concerns at any time about our privacy policy or the use of your personal information, please contact us on +61 2 9550 7777.
Copyright © 2020 Pearsons Florist. All rights reserved.
